<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuide</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="place_thumbnail_image">Place ThumbNail Image</string>
    <string name="place_name">PLACE NAME</string>
    <string name="phone_no">Not Available</string>
    <string name="nearest_metro">Nearest Metro : </string>
    <string name="metro_dist_text">Distance From Nearest Metro : </string>

    <string-array name="namesOfMonuments">
        <item>GURUDWARA BANGLA SAHIB</item>
        <item>HUMAYUN\'S TOMB</item>
        <item>INDIA GATE</item>
        <item>JAMA MASJID</item>
        <item>JANTAR MANTAR</item>
        <item>LODI GARDENS</item>
        <item>LOTUS TEMPLE</item>
        <item>QUTAB MINAR</item>
        <item>RED FORT</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="nearestMetroOfMonuments">
        <item>Patel Chowk</item>
        <item>Khan Market, Jangpura</item>
        <item>Central Secretariat</item>
        <item>Chandhni Chowk</item>
        <item>Rajiv Chowk</item>
        <item>JLN Metro Station</item>
        <item>Nehru Place, Kalkaji</item>
        <item>Qutab Minar</item>
        <item>Chandhni Chowk</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="distanceFromNearestMetroOfMonuments">
        <item>300m</item>
        <item>1km</item>
        <item>900m</item>
        <item>500m</item>
        <item>300m</item>
        <item>500m</item>
        <item>300m</item>
        <item>1.9km</item>
        <item>300m</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="addressOfMonuments">
        <item>Ashok Road, Connaught Place, New Delhi 110001</item>
        <item>Mathura Road, Nizamuddin, New Delhi, 110013</item>
        <item>Rajpath, New Delhi 110001</item>
        <item>Opp. Netaji Subhas marg, Post Kasturba Hospital Marg, Opp. Menna Bazar, Near Red Fort, Chandni Chowak</item>
        <item>Sansad Marg, Connaught Place , New Delhi 110001</item>
        <item>Main Lodi Road, Besides India International Center, New Delhi 110003</item>
        <item>Lotus temple Road, Post Sambhu Dayal Bagh, Bahapur, Kalkaji, New Delhi 110019</item>
        <item>Mehrauli, New Delhi 110030</item>
        <item>Netaji Shubhas Road, Chandani Chowk, New Delhi 110006</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="discriptionOfMonuments">
        <item>It is One of the Most scarosanct Sikh places of worship in Delhi, associated with 8thSikh Guru, Guru Harikrishan
        . The Pond inside its complex, known as \"Sarovar\" is considered holy by the Sikhs.</item>
        <item>Humayun's tomb is the tomb of the Mughal Emperor Humayun in Delhi, India. The tomb was commissioned by
            Humayun's first wife and chief consort, Empress Bega Begum, in 1569-70, and designed by Mirak Mirza</item>
        <item>The India Gate is a war memorial located astride the Rajpath, on the eastern edge of the "ceremonial axis"
            of New Delhi, India, formerly called Kingsway</item>
        <item>The Masjid-i Jahān-Numā (Persian/Urdu: مسجدِ جہاں نما, Devnagri: मस्जिद जहान नुमा, the 'World-reflecting Mosque'),
            commonly known as the Jama Masjid devnagrii: जामा मस्जिद, Urdu: جامع مسجد) of Delhi, is one of the largest mosques
            in India. It was built by Mughal Emperor Shah Jahan between 1644 and 1656 at a cost of 1 million rupees, and was
            inaugurated by an Imam from Bukhara, present-day Uzbekistan.</item>
        <item>Jantar Mantar is located in the modern city of New Delhi. It consists of 13 architectural astronomy instruments.</item>
        <item>Lodi Gardens or Lodhi Gardens is a city park situated in New Delhi, India. Spread over 90 acres, it contains,
            Mohammed Shah's Tomb, Tomb of Sikandar Lodi, Shisha Gumbad and Bara Gumbad, architectural</item>
        <item>The Lotus Temple, located in Delhi, India, is a Bahá'í House of Worship that was dedicated in December 1986,
            costing $10 million. Notable for its flowerlike shape, it has become a prominent attraction in the city.</item>
        <item>The Qutub Minar, also spelled as Qutab Minar, or Qutb Minar, is the tallest minaret in the world made
            up of bricks. The minaret forms a part of the Qutab complex, a UNESCO World Heritage Site in the Mehrauli area of Delhi,
            India.</item>
        <item>Red Fort is a historic fort in the city of Delhi in India. It was the main residence of the emperors of the Mughal
            dynasty for nearly 200 years, until 1856. It is located in the center of Delhi and houses a number of museums. </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nameOfMalls">
        <item>AMBIENCE MALL GURUGAON</item>
        <item>DLF MALL NOIDA</item>
        <item>GIP MALL NOIDA</item>
        <item>LOGIX MALL NOIDA</item>
        <item>OPULENT MALL GHAZIABAD</item>
        <item>WAVE MALL NOIDA</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="nearestMetroToMalls">
        <item>SIKANDARPUR</item>
        <item>SECTOR 18 NOIDA</item>
        <item>SECTOR 18 NOIDA</item>
        <item>WAVE CITY CENTER NOIDA</item>
        <item>NO METRO</item>
        <item>SECTOR 18 NOIDA</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="distFromMetroMalls">
        <item>900m</item>
        <item>700m</item>
        <item>450m</item>
        <item>100m</item>
        <item>N/A</item>
        <item>700m</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="phoneNoOfMalls">
        <item>01244737101</item>
        <item>01206209972</item>
        <item>01204650300</item>
        <item>01202471552</item>
        <item>08287120120</item>
        <item>01204364666</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="addressOfMalls">
        <item>NH 8, Ambience Island, DLF Phase 3, Sector 24, Gurugram, Haryana 122002</item>
        <item>Sector 18, Noida, Uttar Pradesh 201301</item>
        <item>Plot No A-2, Sector 38-A, Noida, Uttar Pradesh 201301</item>
        <item> Plot No. BW-58, Golf Marg, Sector 32, Near Noida City Centre Metro Station, Noida, Uttar Pradesh 201301</item>
        <item>C-115, Grand Trunk Road, East Model Town, Nehru Nagar III, Nehru Nagar, Ghaziabad, Uttar Pradesh 201001</item>
        <item>Pocket J, Sector 18, Noida, Uttar Pradesh 201301</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="discriptionOfMalls">
        <item>Ambience Mall, Gurgaon is a shopping mall in Gurgaon, Haryana, India. It contains an area of 1,997,378 square feet.
            Most floors have a shopping area of 860 meters. Ambience Mall has more than 230 stores and food outlets.</item>
        <item>DLF Mall of India, is a shopping mall in India located in Noida NCR, Uttar Pradesh. It is spread
            across the retail space of 2 million. The mall is divided in 5 zones spread over 7 floors.</item>
        <item>The Great India Place is a shopping mall in Noida, Uttar Pradesh, India. It is popularly known as GIP Mall.
            It is one of the largest malls in the country. The mall features a wide selection of national and international
            retail outlets</item>
        <item>Logix City Centre is one of the most prominently located Commercial Property in Noida Extension, NCR.
            The mall ensures sterling Shopping and entertainment</item>
        <item>Not Available</item>
        <item>With cutting edge infrastructure, technology and management, Wave Malls are the one-stop destination
            for shopping, entertainment and food in Noida, India.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nameOfHotels">
        <item>Goldfinch Hotel Faridabad</item>
        <item>Hotel Aman Continental</item>
        <item>Piccadily Hotel</item>
        <item>Radission Plaza Hotel</item>
        <item>The Taj Mahal Hotel New Delhi</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="neatrestMetroToHotels">
        <item>N/A</item>
        <item>New Delhi Metro</item>
        <item>New Delhi Metro</item>
        <item>Rajiv Chowk Metro</item>
        <item>N/A</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="distNearMetroOfHotels">
        <item>N/A</item>
        <item>1.5km</item>
        <item>250m</item>
        <item>700m</item>
        <item>N/A</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="phoneOfHotels">
        <item>01294249999</item>
        <item>01294249999</item>
        <item>01141234123</item>
        <item>01126779191</item>
        <item>01166566162</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="addressOfHotels">
        <item>Goldfinch Hotel, Sector 39, Surajkund, Faridabad, Surajkund, Faridabad, Haryana, 121010</item>
        <item>1048, Main Bazar, Paharganj. 5 Minutes Walk To New Delhi Railway Station. Delhi India 110055</item>
        <item> Centre Complex Block A1, Janakpuri District Center, Janakpuri, New Delhi, Delhi 110058</item>
        <item>Near Mahipalpur Extension Nh 8, New Delhi, Delhi 110037</item>
        <item>No.1, Man Singh Road, New Delhi, Delhi 110001</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="discriptionOfHotels">
        <item>Goldfinch hotel in Surajkund is situated in the business district, close to Faridabad toll plaza and metro station,
            which puts NCR within easy reach.</item>
        <item>Enjoy your stay in luxury Hotel in New Delhi. Book  Hotel room
            online and get best offers along with wide range of luxury star facilities.</item>
        <item>Enjoy your stay in luxury Hotel in, New Delhi. Book Piccadily Hotel room online and get best offers along
            with wide range of luxury star facilities.</item>
        <item>Reserve a room at the five-star Radisson Blu near the airport in New Delhi to enjoy on-site dining,
            a free-form pool and a spa. Book your hotel room today!</item>
        <item>Experience the buzz of the capital in an effortlessly elegant manner at some of the best luxury hotels in New Delhi</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nameOfNightLife">
        <item>Blu O</item>
        <item>Hauz Khas Village</item>
        <item>House A</item>
        <item>India Gate</item>
        <item>Kitty Su</item>
        <item>Mocha Art House</item>
        <item>Murthal</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="nearestMetroNight">No Metro Service At Night</string>
    <string name="disnearestMetroNight">No Metro</string>
    <string-array name="phoneOfNightPlace">
        <item>01123456789</item>
        <item>N/A</item>
        <item>01166771308</item>
        <item>N/A</item>
        <item>01144447666</item>
        <item>09069138193</item>
        <item>N/A</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="addressOfNightPlace">
        <item>2, Nelson Mandela Marg, Vasant Kunj II, Vasant Kunj, New Delhi, Delhi 110070</item>
        <item>Hauz Khas Village, delhi</item>
        <item>Hyatt Regency Delhi, Bhikaji Cama Place, New Delhi, Delhi 110066</item>
        <item>India gate, janpath, New Delhi</item>
        <item>The Lalit Hotel, Barakhamba Road, Opp Modern School, Connaught Place, New Delhi, Delhi 110001</item>
        <item>167, DLF Promenade, Nelson Mandela Road, Vasant Kunj II, New Delhi, Delhi 110070</item>
        <item>13 km north of Sonipat,50 kilometers from the national capital New Delhi</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="discpOfNightPlace">
        <item>This place is famous among the children as this place is a game zone of the Ambience Mall in Gurgaon, Delhi.
            This is a perfect place for the people who love bowling. This place is also regarded as the best bowling place of Delhi.</item>
        <item>With a beautiful scenic view of a lake and a unique presentation this place has been a very happening destination, since it started.</item>
        <item>This place is very famous for its interior décor. This place is a famous destination for the nightlife in Delhi.
            The heavenly lighting of this place which is done with the help of colorful lights makes this place a
            nice choice for nightlife in Delhi for singles and also for couples. This </item>
        <item>Located on the sides of Rajpath, the road near India Gate is very romantic and is a perfect choice for the couples who are in a
            mood of a night walk. One can be here with his partner or friend and can taste the local flavors of our country</item>
        <item>With an energetic music, a magnetic dance floor and a great collection of cocktails being served this place becomes one’s
            first choice to experience the nightlife in Delhi.</item>
        <item>This place is for the cricket lovers in Delhi. Here one can have late night dinner with friends and can enjoy a cricket
            match in big LED screen. This place is famous for the sizzlers which are served during the match and for other food items too.</item>
        <item>At a distance of around 60 kilometers from the city this is quite a different place is located. Travel time which is around 2 to 2.5 hours,
            is a worth ride as one gets to taste the parathas drowned in butter with different stuffing according to the person’s choice.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="nearestMetroText">Nearest Metro Station :</string>
    <string name="nearestMetroDistance">Distance From Nearest Metro Station :</string>
    <string name="phoneNoText">Phone No. :</string>
    <string name="address">Address :</string>
    <string name="discrip">Discription :</string>

    <string-array name="tabLayoutTitles">
        <item>MONUMENTS</item>
        <item>MALLS</item>
        <item>HOTELS</item>
        <item>NIGHT PLACES</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>